Will your job be done by a robot in the future?
未来你的工作会被机器人取代吗？
Bank of England economists predict that almost half of all UK jobs are under threat of automation.
英格兰银行的经济学家预测，英国几乎一半的工作都面临着自动化的威胁。
Those most at risk involve repetitive manual labour, such as factory positions.
那些处境最危险的工作涉及重复性的体力劳动，比如工厂里的岗位。
But could even the venerable profession of teaching soon have to compete against powerful electronic educators?
但就连令人尊敬的教学职业，是否很快也得与强大的电子教育者竞争呢？
At first glance, teaching might seem impervious to replacement by robots.
乍一看，教学似乎不会被机器人所取代。
Teachers use a range of soft skills that machines find hard to replicate.
教师运用一系列机器难以复制的软技能。
They gauge pupils‘ needs and tailor feedback accordingly.
他们评估学生的需求，并相应地调整反馈。
They adapt materials to make them more engaging and effective.
他们对教学材料进行改编，使其更具吸引力和效果。
And they provide pastoral care: looking out for students who lag behind or disrupt the class.
而且他们还提供精神关怀：关注那些落后或扰乱课堂秩序的学生。
Nonetheless, some believe the future of education will be technological.
尽管如此，一些人认为教育的未来将是科技化的。
In an interview with Business Insider magazine, futurist Thomas Frey predicts that “by 2030 the largest company on the internet is going to be an education-based company that we haven’t heard of yet.”
未来学家托马斯·弗雷在接受《商业内幕》杂志采访时预测：“到2030年，互联网上最大的公司将是一家我们尚未听说过的以教育为基础的公司。”
He thinks that ’bots’ - online robot teachers - will make education so efficient that students will be able to compress an entire undergraduate degree into six months of learning.
他认为，“机器人”——在线机器人教师——将使教育变得如此高效，以至于学生能够将整个本科学位课程压缩到六个月的学习时间内。
A bot learns what your “idiosyncrasies” “interests” and “reference points” are, “and it figures out how to teach you in a faster and faster way over time,” according to Frey.
据弗雷说，一个机器人会了解你的“个人特质”、“兴趣”和“参照点”，“并且随着时间的推移，它会想出越来越快的方式来教你”。
Whether or not such incredible speeds will be reached, over the last decade there has been a huge increase in online learning platforms.
不管是否能达到如此惊人的速度，在过去十年里，在线学习平台大幅增加。
Companies such as Udemy and Khan Academy produce courses that allow millions to learn at home for free, at their own pace.
像Udemy和可汗学院这样的公司制作的课程，让数百万人能够在家以自己的节奏免费学习。
But there are limitations.
但这也存在局限性。
Without the face-to-face stimulation of a classroom environment, the overwhelming majority of students fail to complete online courses.
没有了课堂环境中面对面的激励，绝大多数学生都无法完成在线课程。
How to sustain motivation to learn is one more skill that online teachers will need to master.
如何保持学习动力是在线教师需要掌握的另一项技能。
Indeed, Frey admits there is some way to go: “Nobody has quite cracked the code for the future of education.”
的确，弗雷承认还有一段路要走：“还没有人完全破解未来教育的密码。”
What do teachers themselves think about this?
教师们自己对此有什么看法呢？
Professor Donald Clark from Derby University in the UK thinks that we should embrace change, even though people will lose their jobs.
英国德比大学的唐纳德·克拉克教授认为，我们应该接受变革，尽管人们会失去工作。
“Artificial intelligence will destroy jobs - so why not use it for a social good such as learning?” he asked.
“人工智能会毁掉工作——那么为什么不把它用于学习这样的社会公益事业呢？”他问道。